A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Administration, Program and Policy, RG 3 FA112
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administration, Program and Policy, 2
  - General Program and Policy, 1913-1991; 900; 99 document cases
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS11, Appendix #7-10d, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 375)
      Pro UnarCS11, appendix #9: Basic Science (Human Nutrition), Nutritional Physiology and Biochemistry, Nutrition and Food Microbiology, Biostatistics, Social Sciences-Psychology, Sociology and Agricultural Economics; No Date
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #10a: Adelola Adeloye; The Ibadan Surgeon, Vol. 1, Number 1; September 1977
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #10b: Adelola Adeloye; The Ibadan Surgeon, Vol. 2, Number 1; March 1978
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #10c: Annual Report of the University College Hospital, Ibadan, Nigeria; 1974-1975
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #10d: Annual Report of the University College Hospital, Ibadan, Nigeria; 1976-1977
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS11, Appendix #11a - Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #19, 1971-1979 (Box 69, Folder 376)
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #11: Publications; No Date
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #11a: Professor Akinyele Fabiyi; Virus Research in Nigeria; June 1971
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #12: Research Papers Published from Ibadan, University of Ibadan, Department of Chemistry; No Date
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #13: Faculty of Medicine (Ibarapa postings), Medical Students Program; 1978/79 Session
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #14: Director, Professor T. O. Ogunlesi; Students at Igbo-Ora, University of Ibadan; 1979
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #15: Director, Professor T. O. Ogunlesi; Students at Igbo-Ora, Triennial Report of Vital Statistics, University of Ibadan; 1979
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #16: Director, Professor T. O. Ogunlesi; Students at Igbo-Ora, Demography of Ibarapa Division, University of Ibadan; 1979
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #17-19: Ibarapa Postings - a Record of the Teaching, Service and Students' Activities during the A74 Postings of Students to Ibarapa; 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS11, Appendix #20, 1979 (Box 69, Folder 377)
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #20: Ibarapa Postings - A Record of the Teaching, Service and Students' Activities during the A74 Postings of Students to Ibarapa; 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS11, Appendix #21 - Pro-CS11, appendix #23, 1977-1978 (Box 69, Folder 378)
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #21: The Relationship Between Ibarapa and the Departments; No Date
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #22: University of Ibadan, Nigeria, Faculty of Medicine, Prospectus; 1977-1978
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #23: Community Medicine, A Joint Venture between the University of Ibadan Medical School and the Ministry of Health, Western State Government, Health Care Reports, Students at Igbo-Ora Research (Brucellosis, Hypertension); April 1972
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS11, Appendix #24 - Pro-CS11, appendix #33, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 379)
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #24: Faculty of Science, Prospectus, University of Ibadan; 1974-1975
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #25: Consideration Relating to a Department of General Practice in a Nigerian Medical School; 1978
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #26: Department of Medical Microbiology, University of Ibadan; September 1973
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #27: Official Opening of the Special Treatment Clinical and Venereal Diseases and Treponematoses Research and Teaching Laboratory; March 10, 1977
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #28: Information Handbook, Department of Pharmacology and Therapeutics, University of Ibadan; 1976
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #29: Department of Preventative and Social Medicine, University of Ibadan; 1948-1973
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #30: Priorities in National Health Planning, Focus on Medical Manpower (summary), University of Ibadan symposium; No Date
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #31: Zacchaeus A. Ademuwagun: Birth of the First Center for Professional Preparation in Health Education in Africa; July-September 1976
      Pro Unar-CS11, appendix #32: Zacchaeus A. Ademuwagun; A Review of the Health Education Activities and Future Needs in Africa; March 1978
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS12 - Pro Unar-CS13, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 380)
      Pro Unar-CS12: Ordway Starnes; Education for Development, The Faculty of Agriculture, Forestry and Veterinary Medicine, University of Imadun, Nigeria; January 1979
      Pro Unar-CS13: John E. Swanson; Education for Development, Administrative Support to the University of Ibadan, Nigeria (an evaluation); January-February 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS14, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 381)
      Pro Unar-CS14: Joseph E. Black; Education for Development, Cooperative Program with University of Ibadan, Nigeria (a review); September 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS16, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 382)
      Pro Unar-CS16: Ordway Starnes; Volume 2, Education for Development in East Africa, the Faculty of Veterinary Medicine, University of Nairobi, Kenya, The Faculty of Agriculture, Makerere University, Uganda; January 4, 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Reports - Pro Unar-CS17 - Pro Unar-CS18, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 383)
      Pro Unar-CS17: David Court (coordinator); Higher Education in East Africa, A Review of Rockefeller Foundation Assistance; Ordway Starnes, Joyce Moock and Joel Barkan; Case Studies; 1979
      Pro Unar-CS18: Edourd Bustin; Education for Development, National University of Zaire (a review); August 1979
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 384)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 385)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 386)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 387)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 388)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Supplementary Material (Box 72, Folder 389)
    - Program and Policy - Underdeveloped Areas - Center Studies - Emmerson, Donald K., Kennedy, John J., 1979 (Box 72, Folder 390)
    - Program and Policy - U. S. Land Use Issues, 1976, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 391)
    - Program and Policy - Weather and Climate, 1974-1976 (Box 72, Folder 392)
    - Program and Policy - Weather and Climate - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 393)
    - Program and Policy - Weather and Climate - Supplementary Material, 1974-1975 (Box 72, Folder 394)
    - Program and Policy - Youth Employment, 1976-1978 (Box 72, Folder 395)
    - Program and Policy - Youth Employment, 1976-1978 (Box 72, Folder 396)
    - Program and Policy - Youth Employment, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 397)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1969-1974, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 398)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1969-1974, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 399)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1969-1974, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 400)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1969-1974, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 401)
    - Tax Reform Act, 1969-1974, 1979 (Box 73, Folder 402)
    - Tax Reform Act - Congress, etc - A-Z, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 403)
    - Tax Reform Act - Congress, etc - A-Z, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 404)
    - Tax Reform Act - Congress, etc - A-Z, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 405)
    - Tax Reform Act - Council on Foundations, 1969-1971 (Box 74, Folder 406)
    - Tax Reform Act - Danforth Foundation, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 407)
    - Tax Reform Act - Legal Analysis A-I, 1969 (Box 74, Folder 408)
    - Tax Reform Act - Legal Analysis - JKS's Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 74, Folder 409)
    - Tax Reform Act - Legal Analysis - Patterson, Belknap and Webb, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 410)
    - Tax Reform Act - Legal Analysis - S-Z, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 411)
    - Tax Reform Act - Press Coverage A-Z, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 412)
    - Tax Reform Act - Press Coverage A-Z, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 413)
    - Tax Reform Act - Testimony - Rockefeller Foundation, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 414)
    - Tax Reform Act - Testimony - Rockefeller Foundation, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 415)
    - Tax Reform Act - Testimony - A-Z, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 416)
    - Tax Reform Act - Testimony - A-Z, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 417)
    - Tax Reform Act - Testimony - A-Z, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 418)
    - Tax Reform Act - A-Z, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 419)
    - Tax Reform Act - A-Z, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 420)
    - Tax Reform Act - Reports - Test-1, 1969 (Box 77, Folder 421)
      Test-1: Tax Reform Act of 1969, Foundations' Coordinated Testimony Group before the Committee on finance of the United States Senate; September 9, 1969
    - Vault, 1913-1914, 1916-1917, 1921-1924, 1926-1954, 1956-1977 (Box 77, Folder 422)
    - Vault, 1913-1914, 1916-1917, 1921-1924, 1926-1954, 1956-1977 (Box 77, Folder 423)
    - Vault, 1913-1914, 1916-1917, 1921-1924, 1926-1954, 1956-1985 (Box 77, Folder 424)
    - Vault - Reports - Vau-1 - Vau-3, 1959, 1962, 1979 (Box 77, Folder 425)
      Vau-1: The Rockefeller Foundation, Secretary's Records, Chase Safe Deposit Vault; July 1959
      Vau-2 DR 960: Agreement for Custody Corporate Account of the Rockefeller Foundation with certification by Secretary of Rockefeller Foundation; May 15, 1962
      Vau-3: The Rockefeller Foundation Out-of-Town Vault; 1970
    - Villa Serbelloni - Grant Actions, 1959-1968 (Box 78, Folder 426)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 427)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 428)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 429)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 430)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1959-1961 (Box 78, Folder 431)
    - Villa Serbelloni, 1962-1967, 1970, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 432)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - Reports - Vil-1 - Vil-2, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 433)
      Vil-1: Principessa della Torre e Tasso; Correspondence and Exhibits Relating to Proposed Bequest of the Villa Serbelloni on Lake Como, Italy to the Rockefeller Foundation; Jun19, 1959
      Vil-2: Principessa della Torre e Tasso; Correspondence and Exhibits Relating to Proposed Bequest of the Villa Serbelloni on Lake Como, Italy to the Rockefeller Foundation; June 19, 1959
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - Reports - Vil-2a - Vil-3b, 1959, 1961-1962 (Box 79, Folder 434)
      Vil-2a: Notes on Villa Serbelloni; Gerald R. Pomerat; 1.) Notes on Bellagio Conference on Program for the Villa, October 2-19, 1959; 2.) Original Memoranda of Consensus; 1959
      Vil-2b: Notes on Villa Serbelloni; Gerald R. Pomerat; 1.) Notes on Bellagio Conference on Program for the Villa, October 2-19, 1959; 2.) Memoranda of Consensus; 1959
      Vil-3: John Marshall; Brief History of the Villa Serbelloni; October 1959
      Vil-3a: John Marshall; Brief History of the Villa Serbelloni, revised; January 1961
      Vil-3b: Storia della Villa Serbelloni; History of the Villa Serbelloni, 1962
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - Reports - Vil-4 - Vil-6, 1962-1963, 1966 (Box 79, Folder 435)
      Vil-4: John Maier; The Villa Serbelloni Program; November 26, 1952
      Vil-5: John Maier; The Villa Serbelloni - A Review of the Period June 1959-December 1963; 1963
      Vil-6: Villa Serbelloni Program - Report to the Trustees of the Rockefeller Foundation; December 5-6, 1966
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material, 1959-1964 (Box 79, Folder 436)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material, 1959-1964 (Box 79, Folder 437)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - Princess Della Torre e Tasso, Probate File, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 438)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material, 1961, 1963 (Box 80, Folder 439)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - John Marshall's History, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 440)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Supplementary Material - Hugh H. Smith's History, [1968?] (Box 81, Folder 441)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 442)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 443)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1959 (Box 81, Folder 444)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 445)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 446)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 447)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 448)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 449)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 450)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1960-June 1961 (Box 82, Folder 451)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 452)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 453)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 454)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 455)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 456)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1961-April 1963 (Box 83, Folder 457)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 458)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 459)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 460)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 461)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 462)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, May 1963-June 1965 (Box 84, Folder 463)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 464)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 465)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 466)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 467)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 468)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 469)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, July 1965-December 1967 (Box 85, Folder 470)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 471)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 472)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 473)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 474)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 475)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration, 1968-1970 (Box 86, Folder 476)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 0476a)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 0476b)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 0476c)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 0476d)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 0476e)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Inventories, c 1968 (Box 086A, Folder 476f)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material, 1959-1970 (Box 086A, Folder 0476g)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Supplementary Material - Insurance/Inventories (Box 086A, Folder 0476h)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Administration - Program Conferences, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 477)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Master - Fellow Meetings - Economic History, 1960-1961 (Box 87, Folder 478)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Master - Fellow Meetings - Legal Philosophy, 1964-1966 (Box 87, Folder 479)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Master - Fellow Meetings - Legal Positivism, 1959-1962 (Box 87, Folder 480)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy - Grant Actions, 1959-1970 (Box 87, Folder 481)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1949, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 482)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1949, 1959-1960 (Box 87, Folder 483)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 484)
      Beginning with 1971, see 120 Program & Policy
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 485)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 486)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 487)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 488)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Program and Policy, 1961-1970 (Box 88, Folder 489)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - A, 1960-1970 (Box 88, Folder 490)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Adlen, John R., 1968-1969 (Box 88, Folder 491)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Alexander, Christopher, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 492)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Avshalomov, Jacob, 1968-1969 (Box 89, Folder 493)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - B, 1960-1970 (Box 89, Folder 494)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - B, 1960-1970 (Box 89, Folder 495)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Ballet, Arthur, 1968 (Box 89, Folder 496)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Beloff, Max, 1963-1971 (Box 89, Folder 497)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Bergin, Thomas G., 1962, 1967-1969 (Box 89, Folder 498)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Bertocci, Peter, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 499)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Bowle, John, 1963-1965 (Box 89, Folder 500)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1961-1964 (Box 89, Folder 501)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Bullock, Alan, 1962-1969 (Box 89, Folder 502)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Burchard, John, 1968-1969, 1975-1977 (Box 89, Folder 503)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Butterfield, Herbert, 1961-1967 (Box 89, Folder 504)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Betterfield, Victor, 1967 (Box 89, Folder 505)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - C, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 506)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - C, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 507)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Carter, Elliot C., 1966-1967, 1970 (Box 90, Folder 508)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Crawford, R. M., 1968-1970 (Box 90, Folder 509)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - D, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 510)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - David, Henry, 1961, 1976 (Box 90, Folder 511)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Detwiler, Henry, 1960-1963 (Box 90, Folder 512)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Deutsch, Karl, 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 90, Folder 513)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Dorati, Antal, 1960-1962 (Box 90, Folder 514)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - E, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 515)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Ecke, Gustav, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder 516)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Eisenstaadt, S. N., 1966-1970 (Box 90, Folder 517)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Else, Gerald F., 1967-1968 (Box 90, Folder 518)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Evans, Arthur W., 1962-1967 (Box 90, Folder 519)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - F, 1960-1970 (Box 90, Folder 520)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Feis, Herbert, 1961-1962 (Box 91, Folder 521)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Fox, William T. R., 1962-1963 (Box 91, Folder 522)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - G, 1960-1970 (Box 91, Folder 523)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Garham, P. C. C., 1961-1965, 1967-1970 (Box 91, Folder 524)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Gibson, James, 1963-1964, 1967 (Box 91, Folder 525)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Gonzales, N. V. M., 1964 (Box 91, Folder 526)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Goodwin, Robert W., 1966-1968 (Box 91, Folder 527)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - H, 1960-1970 (Box 91, Folder 528)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - H, 1960-1970 (Box 91, Folder 529)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Hancock, Keith, 1962-1967 (Box 91, Folder 530)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Holton, Gerald, 1968 (Box 91, Folder 531)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Hook, Sidney, 1964-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 532)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - I-J, 1960-1970 (Box 91, Folder 533)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Jellife, D. B., 1966-1968 (Box 91, Folder 534)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Jones, W. T., 1965-1966, 1969-1970 (Box 91, Folder 535)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - K, 1960-1970 (Box 91, Folder 536)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Korbel, Josef, 1969-1971 (Box 92, Folder 537)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Katz, Milton, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 538)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Kelly, John N. D., 1966-1967, 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 539)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Kertesz, Stephen D., 1964-1967 (Box 92, Folder 540)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - L, 1960-1970 (Box 92, Folder 541)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Lane, Robert E., 1965-1967 (Box 92, Folder 542)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Leach, Richard H., 1966-1968, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 543)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Lockwood, William W., 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 544)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Loosjes, Theodor P., 1964-1966, 1968 (Box 92, Folder 545)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Luening, Otto, 1965-1967, 1971, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 546)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - M, 1960-1970 (Box 92, Folder 547)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Machlup, Fritz, 1964, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 548)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - McLellan, David S., 1969-1970 (Box 92, Folder 549)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Marjolin, Robert, 1965-1966 (Box 92, Folder 550)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Markham, F. M. H., 1960-1962, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 551)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Martin, John B., 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 552)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Melden, A. I., 1961-1962, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 553)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Mattingly, Garrett, 1960-1961 (Box 92, Folder 554)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Meredith, William, 1968-1970 (Box 92, Folder 555)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Miller, John Perry, 1967-1968 (Box 92, Folder 556)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Mirsky, Jeanette, 1961-1962, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 557)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Mizner, Arthur, 1965 (Box 93, Folder 558)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Morganthau, Hans J., 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 559)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Morris, Richard, 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 560)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Morse, Arthur D., 1965-1967 (Box 93, Folder 561)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - N, 1961, 1952 (Box 93, Folder 562)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Neustadt, Richard, 1964-1967 (Box 93, Folder 563)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Norrington, A. L. P., 1967-1968 (Box 93, Folder 564)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - O, 1960-1970 (Box 93, Folder 565)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - P, 1960-1970 (Box 93, Folder 566)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Penfield, Wilder, 1961-1962 (Box 93, Folder 567)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Perkins, James, 1964-1969 (Box 93, Folder 568)
    - Villa Serbelloni - Scholars - Philip, P. J., 1964-1965 (Box 93, Folder 569)